Preliminary Guide to The Thomas Hahn Chesapeake and Ohio Canal collection, 1939-1993 MS2020
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Large format negative of bridges over waterway, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 25)
- Large format negative of canal boats in C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 26)
- Large format negative of C&PRR - Cumberland Wharf - Canal boats in C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 27)
- Large format negative of mule pulling canal boat in the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 28)
- Large format negative of canal boats lines up on C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 29)
- Large format negative of point along the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 30)
- Large format negative of two men in front of bridge to Georgetown with Georgetown in the background, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 31)
- Large format negative of canal barge coming out of the Paw Paw Tunnel on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 32)
- Large format negative of large wooden building, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 33)
- Large format negative of wooden buildings at lock on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 34)
- Large format negative of wooden building, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 35)
- Large format negative of lock on C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 36)
- Large format negative of mules pulling canal barges on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 37)
- Large format negative of C&O Canal and Potomac River at Williamsport, MD., undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 38)
- Large format negative of mechanical bridge over the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 39)
- Large format negative of an overhead view of a canal barge in a lock on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 40)
- Large format negative of canal barges on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 41)
- Large format negative of lock on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 42)
- Large format negative of view of Harper's Ferry, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 43)
- Large format negative of a lock and buildings on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 44)
- Large format negative of canal barges and mules on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 45)
- Large format negative of Harper's Ferry, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 46)
- Large format negative of Harper's Ferry, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 47)
- Large format negative of view of the island, Virginius, in the Shenandoah, at Harper's Ferry taken near Jefferson Rock, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 48)
- Large format negative of buildings along the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 49)
- Large format negative of buildings along the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 50)
- Large format negative of masonry structure on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 51)
- Large format negative of buildings near waterway, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 52)
- Large format negative of lock and buildings on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 53)
- Large format negative of Georgetown on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 54)
- Large format negative of Canal Towage Co. No.93 on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 55)
- Large format negative of lock and building on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 56)
- Large format negative of canal barges and buildings on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 57)
- Large format negative of lock on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 58)
- Large format negative of canal barge going through lock on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 59)
- Large format negative of canal barge going through lock next to a lock house on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 60)
- Large format negative of canal, buildings, and railroad trellis bridge, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 61)
- Large format negative of the plan for the incline plan, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 62)
- Large format negative of the Outlet Incline on the C&O Canal, 1876 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 63)
- Large format negative of canal barge going through a lock on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 64)
- Large format negative of a rock formation, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 65)
- Large format negative of handwritten document, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 66)
- Large format negative of canal and lock with lock house, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 67)
- Large format negative of people at Great Falls Tavern, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 68)
- Large format negative of building flooded, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 69)
- Large format negative of Aqueduct over waterway, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 70)
- Large format negative of Pontoon Bridge across Potomac River at Berlin October, 1862 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 71)
- Large format negative of canal barge on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 72)
- Large format negative of view from the canal of a lock on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 73)
- Large format negative of lock and lock house on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 74)
- Large format negative of Snyder's Landing, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 75)
- Large format negative of wooded area and masonry with drop off to waterway, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Box 76)
- Large format negative of wooden building, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 77)
- Large format negative of Great Falls Inn & Iron Foundry Ruins, great Falls of the Potomac Va. 15 miles from Washington, dc on the Washington & Old Dominion Railway, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 78)
- Large format negative of letter from Office of the Albemarle & Chesapeake Canal Co. Norfolk, Va 2 June, 1879 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 79)
- Large format negative of railroad Station, Great Falls, VA, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 80)
- Large format negative of lock and boat, Alexandria Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 81)
- Large format negative of Dock, Alexandria Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 82)
- Large format negative of graphic with lock canal boat and railroad, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 83)
- Large format negative of letter from President's office of the Chesapeake and Ohio Canal Company Hagerstown, Washington County, Md. January 4, 1870 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 84)
- Large format negative of little girl with mule and canal barge on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 85)
- Large format negative of the seal of the Chesapeake and Ohio Canal Company, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 86)
- Large format negative of papers of the Chesapeake and Ohio Canal Company, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 87)
- Large format negative of graphic of canal boat and train, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 88)
- Large format negative of woman standing in front of canal barge on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 89)
- Large format negative of two women on canal barge on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 90)
- Large format negative of part of the C&O Canal with lock and bridge, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 91)
- Large format negative of lock keeper's house, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 92)
- Large format negative of boats on canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 93)
- Large format negative of canal barge James E. O'Day on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 94)
- Large format negative of canal barges on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 95)
- Large format negative of bridge over waterway, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 96)
- Large format negative of canal barge and lock keeper's house on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 97)
- Large format negative of Lock 13 on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 98)
- Large format negative of falls entrance at Great Falls, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 99)
- Large format negative of Harper's Ferry, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 100)
- Large format negative of Harper's Ferry, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 101)
- Large format negative of lock and waterway, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 102)
- Large format negative of lock and waterway, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 103)
- The Story of the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 104)
- Mule carrying bundles, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 105)
- People walking in forest, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 106)
- Wagon train in mountains, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 107)
- Map of old roads in Early America, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 108)
- Field and waterway in the distance, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 109)
- Boating the James, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 110)
- Boats meet wagon train, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 111)
- Person in woods with horse, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 112)
- People in colonial garb next to cannons, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 113)
- George Washington's Potowmack Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 114)
- Great Falls, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 115)
- People in colonial attire, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 116)
- Route of the Potowmack Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 117)
- Waterway, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 118)
- Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 119)
- Bridge over waterway, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 120)
- People in colonial attire, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 121)
- People at falls, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 122)
- Rocks and water, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 123)
- Waterway, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 124)
- Stonework, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 125)
- Building a lock, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 126)
- Chiseled markings on a rock, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 127)
- People on water, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 128)
- Modes of transportation, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 129)
- Barge pulled on canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 130)
- Barge and other boat on canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 131)
- Map of canals, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 132)
- Barge being transported, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 133)
- Barge being placed on canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 134)
- Barge being transported by rail, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 135)
- Barge being transported through tunnel, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 136)
- Waterway, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 137)
- Barges on canal near buildings, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 138)
- Barge on canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 139)
- The Old Ditch, 1828-1924, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 140)
- Seal of the Chesapeake and Ohio Canal Company, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 141)
- Chesapeake and Ohio Canal National Historic park 184.5 miles, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 142)
- John Quincy Adams, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 143)
- Canal Groundbreaking ceremony, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 144)
- Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 145)
- Constructing canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 146)
- Early Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 147)
- Railroad and canal barge, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 148)
- Railroad trestle and canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 149)
- Constructing canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 150)
- Barges on canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 151)
- People fighting, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 152)
- Dam, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 153)
- Road cut, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 154)
- Paw Paw Tunnel, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 155)
- Paw Paw Tunnel, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 156)
- Waterway near buildings, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 157)
- Bridge or aqueduct, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 158)
- Bridge or aqueduct, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 159)
- Stonework tunnel, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 160)
- Stonework tunnel, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 161)
- Stonework and waterway, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 162)
- Dam, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 163)
- Stonework and waterway, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 164)
- Stonework waterway and bridge, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 165)
- Stonework and building, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 166)
- Bridge and stonework in winter, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 167)
- Wooden building, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 168)
- Great Falls Tavern and Lock, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 169)
- Canal barge and railcar working, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 170)
- Canal barges on canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 171)
- Barge on canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 172)
- Building on canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 173)
- Building on canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 174)
- Barge on canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 175)
- Barge on canal with stonework and buildings, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 176)
- Great Falls Tavern and Lock, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 177)
- People firing cannons, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 178)
- Side of canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 179)
- Barges, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 180)
- People working, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 181)
- People inside house, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 182)
- Barge at Lock, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 183)
- Mule pulling barge, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 184)
- Photo of person on barge taken from the boat, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 185)
- Mules, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 186)
- Barge and mule, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 187)
- Barge on canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 188)
- Barge on canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 189)
- Man blowing horn, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 190)
- Barge on canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 191)
- House at lock, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 192)
- House at Lock, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 193)
- Barge on canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 194)
- Barge on canal aqueduct, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 195)
- Dam, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 196)
- The End, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 197)
- Photograph of historical marker on the restored section of the original Erie Canal. May, 1974 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 198)
- Photograph of Erie Canal (original) Fort Bull Rome, NY. Independence. May, 1974 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 199)
- Photograph of John Atkinson 'saving' the Independence. May, 1974 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 200)
- Photograph of team towing Independence on restored section of original Erie Canal near Rome, NY. May, 1974 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 201)
- Photograph on top of Independence on restored section of the original Erie Canal near Rome, NY. May, 1974 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 202)
- Photograph of Potomac canal lock at Fletchers. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 203)
- Photograph of Potomac canal lock at Fletchers. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 204)
- Photograph of Potomac canal lock at Fletchers. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 205)
- Photograph of Potomac canal lock at Fletchers. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 206)
- Photograph of model at Great Falls, MD Sybil Ann. December, 1975 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 207)
- Photograph of Sybil Ann, Great Falls, Maryland Museum. December, 1975 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 208)
- Photograph of cable foot bridge at Great Falls. C&O Canal Historic (74-105). Please credit National Park Service Photo E.B. Thompson, Historic Negative Collection circa, ca. 1928 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 209)
- Photograph of house at Lock 51 (122.59). December, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 210)
- Photograph of Tonoloway Creek aqueduct (No. 7) (122.96). December, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 211)
- Photograph of Lock 52 (122.89). December, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 212)
- Photograph of McCoy's Ferry, C&O Canal. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 213)
- Photograph of the Guard Lock (184.50) "The end of the Canal" April, 1974 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 214)
- Photograph of Lock House 36. January, 1960 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 215)
- Photograph of Lock House 49 (106.80). January, 1960 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 216)
- Photograph of Lock House 52. January, 1960 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 217)
- Repair shed, Lock 66. January, 1960 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 218)
- Lock House 68. January, 1960 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 219)
- C& O Canal Lock House 71 front view. September, 1959 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 220)
- Lock House 52. January, 1960 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 221)
- Section House Lock 39. April, 1960 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 222)
- Building Lock 72. January, 1960 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 223)
- Lock House 44. January, 1960 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 221, Folder 224)
- Tide Lock 0.00. Down river, upper gate pocket, 1973 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 225)
- Point of Rocks railroad station. May, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 226)
- Mouth of Monocacy Post Office and Spellman Store. April, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 227)
- House at Lock 74. April, 1974 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 228)
- Lock house. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 229)
- Lock house in flood., 1972 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 230)
- Lock house., 1972 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 231)
- Lock house., 1972 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 232)
- Flooded road., 1972 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 233)
- Loc 6 Parking flooded., 1972 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 234)
- Mill site sign. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 235)
- Holding Basin sign. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 236)
- Potomac River at Great Falls. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 237)
- Guard Gate sign. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 238)
- Potomac River at Great Falls. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 239)
- Large eye bolt in rock near Great Falls. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 240)
- Lock with canal boat and mules. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 241)
- Canal boat with mules going over an aqueduct. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 242)
- Canal boat going through a lock. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 243)
- Woman standing on aqueduct. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 244)
- Lock. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 245)
- Swinging wagon Bridge at Lock no. 25 (Edward's Ferry). NPS Restoration., 1939 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 246)
- Stop lock and winch house at Dam number 4 below Williamsport, MD. It is...frontal that in the flood of 1936 which destroyed this section of the dam, this little building was submerged to within 18 inches of its ridge and survived. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 247)
- Eight Mile Level above Seneca with canal boat and mules. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 248)
- Eight Mile Level above Seneca with canal boat and mules. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 249)
- Canal boat on canal. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 250)
- Lock 41/42 with canal boat on canal. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 251)
- Canal boat on canal under bridge. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 252)
- Lock 56. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 253)
- Potomac Canal, Great Falls, VA. September, 1974 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 254)
- Potomac Canal, Great Falls, VA. September, 1974 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 255)
- View of the canal. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 256)
- View of the canal. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 257)
- Canal at Hancock, MD. Print reversed. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 258)
- Canal at Hancock, MD. Early 1900's, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 259)
- Lock 58. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 260)
- Lock 64 2/3. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 261)
- East end of the Paw Paw tunnel. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 262)
- lived Lock head of 1 mile level. Print reversed. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 263)
- Frame house #2 Great Falls S. elevation., 1938-1939 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 264)
- Chimney of Inn at Lock 38. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 265)
- Chimney of Inn at Lock 38. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 266)
- Lock 38 from Dumsey Bridge. May, 1974 (Box SHARED Box 18, Folder 21, Folder 267)
- Lock 30 (Brunswick, Maryland). Lock was extended upstream in the 1870's to accommodate an extra boat through the lock to expedite locking through time. Of the extended locks, most were extended downstream which was a much simpler conversion to this type lock. Note also the pivot (swing)., 1900-1920 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 268)
- Canal (lock) wall. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 269)
- Canal (lock) wall. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 270)
- Canal (lock) wall. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 271)
- Canal (lock) wall. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 272)
- Canal (lock) wall. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 273)
- Point of Rocks Bridge. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 274)
- Point of Rocks Bridge. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 275)
- Train along canal. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 276)
- C&O Canal at Harpers Ferry. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 277)
- Lock 33., 1900 ca. (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 278)
- Falls., 1964 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 279)
- Lock 36. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 280)
- Potomac Refining Company. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 281)
- Bridge. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 282)
- Bridge. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 283)
- Lock 38 looking downstream from towpath. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 284)